♪ Peace up, A-Town down ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Okay ♪
♪ Usher, Usher, Usher ♪
♪ Lil Jon ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ Up in the club with my homies ♪
♪ Trying to get a little V-I ♪
♪ But keep it down on the low key ♪
♪ You should know how it feels ♪
♪ I saw this shorty, she
was checking up on me ♪
♪ From the game she was
spitting in my ear ♪
♪ You would think that she knew me ♪
♪ I decided to chill ♪
♪ Okay ♪
♪ Conversation got heavy ♪
♪ She had me feeling like
she's ready to blow ♪
♪ What ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ She was saying come get me ♪
♪ So I got up and followed
her to the floor ♪
♪ She said, baby, let's go,
that's when I told her ♪
♪ I said ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Shorty got down low and
said come and get me ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ I got so caught up
I forgot she told me ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Her and my girl used to
be the best of homies ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Next thing I knew she was
all up on me screaming ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ So she's all up in my head ♪
♪ Got me thinking that
it might be a good idea ♪
♪ To take her with me ♪
♪ 'Cause she's ready to leave ♪
♪ But I gotta keep it real now ♪
♪ 'Cause on a one to 10,
she's a certified 20 ♪
♪ But that just ain't me ♪
♪ 'Cause I don't know
if I take that chance ♪
♪ Just where it's gonna lead ♪
♪ But what I do know
is the way she dance ♪
♪ Makes shorty all right with me ♪
♪ The way she get low, I'm like, yeah ♪
♪ Just work that out for me ♪
♪ She asked for one more
dance and I'm like, yeah ♪
♪ How the hell am I supposed to leave ♪
♪ Let's go, bring the beat back ♪
♪ And I said yeah ♪
♪ Shorty got down low and
said come and get me ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ I got so caught up,
I forgot she told me ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Her and my friend used
to be the best of homies ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Next thing I knew, she
was all up on me screaming ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ Hey, Luda ♪
♪ Watch out, my outfit's ridiculous ♪
♪ In the club looking so conspicuous ♪
♪ And rawr, these women all on the prowl ♪
♪ If you hold the head
steady, I'ma milk the cow ♪
♪ And forget about game,
I'ma spit the truth ♪
♪ I won't stop 'til I get
them in they birthday suit ♪
♪ So give me the rhythm and
it'll be off with their clothes ♪
♪ Then bend over to the
front and touch your toes ♪
♪ I left the Jag and I took the Rolls ♪
♪ If they ain't cutting then
I put them on foot patrol ♪
♪ How you like me now ♪
♪ When my pinky's valued over 300,000 ♪
♪ Let's drink, you the one to please ♪
♪ Ludacris fill cups like double Ds ♪
♪ Me and Ursh once me
and we leaves them dead ♪
♪ We want a lady in the street
but a freak in the bed ♪
♪ That say ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Shorty got down low and
said come and get me ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ I got so caught up,
I forgot she told me ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Her and my girl used to
be the best of homies ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Next thing I knew she was
all up on me screaming ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ Take that and rewind it back ♪
♪ Lil Jon got the beat
that make your booty go ♪
♪ Take that and rewind it back ♪
♪ Usher got the voice
that make your booty go ♪
♪ Take that and rewind it back ♪
♪ Ludacris got the flow
that make your booty go ♪
♪ Take that and rewind it back ♪
♪ Lil Jon got the beat
that make your booty go ♪
♪ Now let me see you do the A-Town stomp ♪
♪ Do the A-Town stomp ♪
♪ Now do the muscle, do the muscle ♪
♪ Do the muscle, do the muscle ♪
♪ Thunderclap, hey ♪
♪ Rock away, rock away,
rock away, rock away ♪
♪ And cut ♪